[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
SURMA: So you're wearing a Christmas hat
SURMA：所以您戴着圣诞帽
because it's Christmas.
因为是圣诞节。
SPEAKER: Yep.
发言者：是的。
SURMA: And as is common in Christmas,
瑟玛：和圣诞节一样，
we're going to talk about 12 things that we're
我们将要谈论的十二件事
excited about for the web.
对网络感到兴奋。
And I thought I would talk about architecture on the web.
我以为我会谈论网络架构。
SPEAKER: OK.
说话者：好的。
Two minutes.
2分钟。
What is that?
那是什么？
Architecture.
建筑。
That's buildings.
那是建筑物。
It's nothing to do with the web, mate.
伙计，这与网络无关。
You got confused.
你很困惑
SURMA: Well, the thing is that lots of other fields,
瑟玛：嗯，问题是还有很多其他领域，
like enterprise engineering and gaming,
像企业工程和游戏，
have like these architectural patterns when they build, like,
在构建时喜欢这些建筑模式，例如，
really complex things.
真的很复杂。
SPEAKER: Nope.
发言者：不。
Fields don't have architecture.
领域没有建筑。
You're thinking of cities.
您正在考虑城市。
SURMA: Software architecture, software engineering.
SURMA：软件体系结构，软件工程。
You come up with patterns to use to compose and combine things
您想出了用于组合和组合事物的模式
and to, you know, like separation
而且，就像分离
of concerns, all these things.
所有这些事情。
And the web hasn't really done that.
网络还没有真正做到这一点。
I mean, you could have done, but developers mostly are like,
我的意思是，您本可以做到的，但是开发人员大多都喜欢，
here's a little app that I built,
这是我构建的一个小应用，
or they just throw things together
或者他们只是把东西放在一起
and do most of the complex stuff in the back end.
并在后端执行大多数复杂的工作。
And I think it's time for the front end developers
我认为现在是前端开发人员的时候了
to have proper architecture in their front end code, as well.
在其前端代码中也具有适当的架构。
SPEAKER: Isn't this what, like, all of the frameworks
发言者：这不是所有框架吗
have been doing forever?
一直在做？
SURMA: Exactly.
苏尔玛：是的。
But I think these patterns should be exposed more
但是我认为这些模式应该更多地暴露
to the developers themselves.
给开发商自己。
For example, what I think that the web has an actor pattern,
例如，我认为网络具有演员模式，
where you have independent threads that are all running
您有正在运行的独立线程
in a single thread mode, but they
在单线程模式下，但是它们
communicate using [INAUDIBLE].
使用[音频不清晰]进行通信。
That's pretty much what we have on the web.
这几乎就是我们网络上的内容。
And that is called an actor pattern,
这就是所谓的演员模式，
but these two things have barely been combined on the web.
但网上几乎没有将这两件事结合在一起。
And I think there's more patterns like this out there
而且我认为还有更多这样的模式
that haven't been applied to the web
尚未应用于网络的内容
to make your front end architecture more manageable
使您的前端架构更易于管理
and nicer to work with.
更好地配合。
SPEAKER: So what do we need to make this work, then?
发言者：那么，我们需要做些什么呢？
SURMA: I think we already have everything
瑟玛：我想我们已经拥有了一切
that we need to make it work, but we
我们需要使其发挥作用，但是我们
haven't started using it.
还没有开始使用它。
Like, we just need to look for the patterns
就像，我们只需要寻找模式
that game engineers use, that enterprise engineers user,
游戏工程师使用的，企业工程师用户使用的，
and see if those are useful for us on the web,
看看这些对我们的网络是否有用，
and try to build things using it.
并尝试使用它来构建事物。
And just experiment.
并进行实验。
SPEAKER: So getting stuff, like, off the main thread
说话者：因此，从主线程中删除东西
except for the UI stuff [INAUDIBLE]??
除了UI内容[听不清]？
SURMA: For example.
SURMA：例如。
That's one thing I want to look into.
这是我要研究的一件事。
And then how do you separate the concerns?
然后您如何区分这些关注点？
What goes onto the off thread, what stays on the main thread?
哪些线程进入关闭线程，哪些线程保留在主线程上？
And then how do you structure your code off thread, as well,
然后，如何在线程外构造代码，
because that's just one big bolt of logic still.
因为那仍然只是逻辑上的一大螺栓。
How do you, like, compose those little bits and bobs
你是如何组成那些小东西的？
[INAUDIBLE]?
[听不清]？
SPEAKER: So in 10 seconds, what should be on the main thread?
发言者：那么在10秒内，主线程上应该是什么？
SURMA: UI work.
SURMA：UI工作。
SPEAKER: Right.
发言者：对。
In six seconds, what shouldn't be on the main thread?
在六秒钟内，主线程上不应该有什么？
SURMA: Not UI work.
SURMA：不支持UI。
SPEAKER: That is correct.
发言者：正确。
Well done.
做得好。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
Nailed it.
搞定了。
I want to talk about weightless CSS.
我想谈谈失重的CSS。
SURMA: Weightless?
瑟玛：失重？
SPEAKER: That is one of the words I said.
说话者：这是我说的一句话。
The other one is CSS.
另一个是CSS。
SURMA: So CSS without weight.
SURMA：所以CSS不重。
SPEAKER: Yes, that is a good reversal of what I said.
发言者：是的，这与我所说的完全相反。
SURMA: What is weight?
瑟玛：什么是体重？